Finding Aid for Medical School (University of Michigan) records, 1850-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Records 1915-1996
  - Administrative Series 1950-1998
    - 1950-1979
      - P
        - General (Box 81)
        - Pharmacy-Medicine-Nursing Conference 1965-1967 (Box 81)
      - R
        - Rare Book Collection 1973-1974 (Box 81)
        - Replacement Hospital Project (see also boxes 157-160)
          - 1968-1970 (Box 81)
          - 1970-1976 (Box 81)
          - 1978
            - General, 2 folders (Box 81)
            - Marketing Questions (Box 81)
            - Miller, Gerald H., Department of Management and Budget, material for (Box 81)
            - Population (Patient) Statistics (Box 81)
            - Progress Report on the Development of a Prospectus (Box 81)
        - Residential College of Medicine, proposal 1965 (Box 81)
        - Retirement Furlough Study 1977 (Box 81)
      - S (Box 82)
        - General (Box 82)
        - Sanger Report, reply to 1958, 1964 (Box 82)
        - Schizophrenia Unit 1961-1963 (Box 82)
        - Shriners Hospital for Crippled Children 1958-1962 (Box 82)
      - T
        - General (Box 82)
        - Toledo Medical School 1965 (Box 82)
      - U
        - General (Box 82)
        - University Hospital
          - Accreditation 1970 (Box 82)
          - Budget
            - Financial Operations Review 1950-1970 (Box 82)
            - 1978, 2 folders (Box 82)
          - Cardiac Study Unit 1970-1972 (Box 82)
          - Correspondence 1960-1969 (Box 82)
          - Director 1969-1971 (Box 82)
          - Holden Prenatal Research Laboratories 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 82)
          - Mott Children's Hospital (dedication) 1969 (Box 82)
          - Renovation 1969-1970 (Box 82)
          - Space Requirements 1960-1962 (Box 82)
          - Tentative Planning Reports 1969, 1975 (Box 82)
        - University Officials, Correspondence and Reports
          - Dean's Annual Report to the President 1940/41-1971/72, 4 folders (Box 82)
          - Fauri, Fedele F., VP State Relations and Planning 1969-1973 (Box 83)
          - Fleming, Robben W., President 1969-1979 (Box 83)
          - Hatcher, Harlan, President 1963-1966 (Box 83)
          - Heyns, Roger W., VP for Academic Affairs 1962-1965 (Box 83)
          - Niehuss, Marvin L., Executive Vice President 1960-1968 (Box 83)
          - Pierpont, Wilbur K., VP and Chief Financial Officer 1967-1976 (Box 83)
          - Rhodes, Frank H. T., VP for Academic Affairs 1974-1977 (Box 83)
          - Smith, Allan F., VP for Academic Affairs 1965-1974, 1979, 6 folders (Box 83)
      - V
        - Veterans Readjustment Center 1944, 1962 (Box 83)
      - W
        - General (Box 83)
    - 1967-1982
      - Accreditation
        - 1967
          - Pre-survey Questionnaire, 2 volumes (Box 156)
          - Correspondence and Memoranda (Box 156)
        - 1975
          (see also box 118)
          - Correspondence and Memoranda, 2 folders (Box 157)
          - Draft Final Report (Box 157)
        - 1979-1980 Self-Study
          - Abstract (Box 157)
          - All Schools and Colleges (Box 157)
          - Medical School (Box 157)
      - Affiliated Hospital's Teaching Costs 1971-1975, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - Appointment and Promotion Activity 1973-1975 (Box 157)
      - Faculty Conference on Curriculum September 15, 1980 (Box 157)
      - Faculty Conference on Education November 1, 1982 (Box 157)
      - Faculty Conference on Promotion Board of Activity October, 1981 (Box 157)
      - Faculty Resignation Analysis 1968-1976 (Box 157)
      - Faculty Sabbatical Reports 1974-1975 (Box 157)
      - Integrated Premedical-Medical Program (Inteflex) 1975 (Box 157)
      - Memorandum of Understanding 1978 (re: role of Medical School) (Box 157)
      - Replacement Hospital Project
        (see also box 81)
        - Bond Issue Steering Committee 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 157)
        - Budget 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 157)
        - Correspondence, Memoranda, etc.
          - 1975-1977 (Box 157)
          - 1978 (Box 157)
          - 1979 (Box 158)
            - January-June (Box 158)
            - July (Box 158)
            - August 1-13 (Box 158)
            - August 14-19 (Box 158)
            - August 20-23 (Box 158)
            - August 23-September 30 (Box 158)
          - 1980
            - January-March (Box 158)
            - April-May, 2 folders (Box 158)
            - June, 2 folders (Box 158)
            - July-August (Box 158)
            - September (Box 158)
            - November-December (Box 158)
          - 1981
            - January-February (Box 158)
            - March (Box 158)
            - April-May (Box 158)
            - June 1-20 (Box 158)
            - June 21-30 (Box 158)
            - July (Box 158)
            - August 1-10 (Box 159)
            - August 11-31 (Box 159)
            - September (Box 159)
            - October (Box 159)
          - 1982 (Box 159)
        - Ground Breaking Ceremony, 2 folders (Box 159)
        - Planning Committee
          - 1977 (Box 159)
          - 1978
            - February-May (Box 159)
            - June (Box 159)
            - July (Box 159)
            - August (Box 159)
            - September (Box 159)
            - October-December (Box 159)
          - 1979
            - January, 2 folders (Box 159)
            - February (Box 159)
            - March (Box 159)
            - April (Box 159)
            - May (Box 159)
            - June 1-20 (Box 159)
            - June 21-30 (Box 159)
            - July 1-25 (Box 160)
            - July 26-August 5 (Box 160)
            - August 6-30 (Box 160)
            - September-December (Box 160)
        - Planning Advisory Committee 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 160)
        - Proposed History (Box 160)
        - Publicity (Box 160)
        - Reports
          - Block Plans for Replacement Hospital May 1980 (Box 160)
          - Certificates of Need
            - Parkview/Turner Hospital February 1979 (Box 160)
            - St. Joseph Mercy January 1979 (Box 160)
            - University Hospital January 1979 (Box 160)
          - Project Suspension Strategies June 1982 (Box 160)
          - Summary of Analytical Study of Reuse of Present Hospital September 12, 1975 (Box 160)
          - Summary of Potential Off-Medical Campus Location October 5, 1975 (Box 160)
          - Working Plan for Location of Hospital October 10, 1975 (Box 160)
        - Review Group June 1980, 3 folders (Box 160)
      - Required Clerkship Phase 1979-1980 (Box 160)
      - Senior Year Curriculum 1974-1975 (Box 160)
      - Study of Medical School Funding 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 160)
    - 1959-1984
      - Ambulatory Care 1962-1965, 1973-1983, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - American Association of Medical Colleges (Box 168)
        - General 1974-1983, 3 folders (Box 168)
        - Enlargement of Medical Student Enrollment 1969 (Box 168)
        - Section 227 1977-1978 (Box 168)
      - American Medical Association-Reports to Council on Medical Education 1964-1979 (Box 168)
      - Administrative Fellows 1982-1987 (Box 168)
      - Awards 1981-1984 (Box 168)
      - Biomedical Research Council
        - General 1973-1984 (Box 168)
        - Dean Search 1974-1975 (Box 168)
      - Buhl Fund 1960-1970 (Box 168)
      - Buhl Research Center for Human Genetics 1960-1968 (Box 168)
      - Burn Center 1976-1983, 3 folders (Box 169)
      - Cancer Planning 1973-1980 (Box 169)
      - Chief of Clinical Affairs 1973-1974 (Box 169)
      - Clinical Research Center
        - General Correspondence
          - 1959-1965 (Box 169)
          - 1973-1984 (Box 169)
        - Policy Committee 1960-1969, 2 folders (Box 169)
        - Operating Committee
          - 1962-1963 (Box 169)
          - 1969-1979 (Box 169)
      - Commencement 1973-1984, 3 folders (Box 169)
      - Committees
        - Admission Committee 1963-1984 (Box 170)
        - Animals, Committee on Use and Care of 1970-1984 (Box 170)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Titles Committee 1968-1977 (Box 178)
        - Bioengineering Committee 1979-1982 (Box 170)
        - Central Tissue Culture Committee 1963-1970 (Box 170)
        - Clinical Teaching Committee 1976 (Box 170)
        - Committee to Review Grants for Clinical Research Involving Human Beings 1969-1972 (Box 170)
        - Dean's Advisory Council 1959 (Box 170)
        - Dental Research Institute, Policy Committee 1971-1984 (Box 170)
        - Fauri Committee Report and Follow-up Recommendations 1972-1973 (Box 170)
        - Financial Aid Committee 1965-1966 (Box 170)
        - Intern Advisory Committee 1969 (Box 170)
        - Neural and Behavioral Sciences Committee 1966-1981 (Box 170)
        - Research in Medical Education Committee 1964-1970 (Box 170)
        - Student Excellence Committee 1964-1970 (Box 170)
        - Student Research Committee 1965-1971 (Box 170)
      - Comprehensive Examinations Report 1959 (Box 170)
      - Consultants in the Medical School 1959 (Box 170)
      - Director of Administrative and Financial Affairs 1980-1984 (Box 170)
      - Financial Development
        - General 1971-1984, 3 folders (Box 170)
        - Advisory Committee 1977-1983 (Box 170)
      - Furstenberg Study Center
        - General 1970-1974 (Box 170)
        - Brochures 1971-1972 (Box 170)
        - Dedication 1974 (Box 170)
        - Fund Raising 1970-1973 (Box 170)
        - Policy Committee 1970-1972 (Box 170)
        - Program and Facilities 1971 (Box 170)
        - Steering Committee 1972-1973 (Box 170)
        - Sponsoring Committee 1972 (Box 170)
      - Gerontology Unit (Box 171)
        - General 1971-1978, 3 folders (Box 171)
        - Scott Turner Bequest 1978-1980 (Box 171)
      - Grand Rapids Area Medical Education Center 1972-1984 (Box 171)
      - Health and Human Values 1974-1979 (Box 171)
      - Health Science Relations 1969-1984, 2 folders (Box 171)
      - Henry Ford Hospital Affiliation
        - Affiliation Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 171)
        - Assistant Dean Search 1975, 1984 (Box 171)
        - Memorandum on a 4-Year School 1962 (Box 171)
        - Correspondence on a 4-Year School 1968 (Box 171)
        - Graduate Medical Education Task Force 1976 (Box 171)
        - Grant Request to R.W. Johnson Foundation 1973-1974 (Box 171)
        - Joint Committee on Affiliation 1974 (Box 171)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Ford Hospital 1962-1980 (Box 171)
        - Task Force to Study Feasibility of Expanded Affiliation 1972 (Box 171)
      - Holden Perinatal Research Labs 1973-1977, 1980-1984, 2 folders (Box 171)
      - Hospital Director
        - Edward J. Connors 1974 (Box 171)
        - Search Committee Report 1969 (Box 171)
        - Search Committee 1975 (Box 171)
      - House Officer Negotiations 1978-1980, 2 folders (Box 172)
      - Inteflex 1974-1984 (Box 172)
      - Inteflex Director 1975-1984 (Box 172)
      - Institutes and Related Units
        - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science 1982-1984 (Box 172)
        - Institute of Gerontology 1978-1984, 2 folders (Box 172)
        - Kresge Foundation 1960-1982 (Box 172)
        - Kresge Hearing Research Institute
          - General 1960-1964, 1974-1984, 2 folders (Box 172)
          - Dedication 1960 (Box 172)
          - Faculty Advisory Committee 1961-1964 (Box 172)
          - Operating Committee 1961-1964 (Box 172)
          - Radioisotope Unit 1959-1963 (Box 172)
          - Visiting Scientific Committee 1960-1964 (Box 172)
        - Mental Health Research Institute
          - General 1965-1984, 2 folders (Box 172)
          - Advisory Committee 1981-1984 (Box 172)
          - Director Selection Committee 1967-1968 (Box 172)
        - Periodic Health Appraisal Unit 1968-1980 (Box 172)
        - Simpson Memorial Institute 1960-1979 (Box 172)
        - Towsley Center for Continuing Medical Education 1966-1973 (Box 172)
        - Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine
          - General 1961-1984, 3 folders (Box 172)
          - Ad Hoc Review Committee for 1972-1973 (Box 173)
          - Budget 1975-1984 (Box 173)
        - Upjohn Center
          - General 1966-1973, 1978-1983, 2 folders (Box 173)
          - Dedication 1970 (Box 173)
          - Faculty Comments on Overhead and UMRI 1960 (Box 173)
          - Operating Committee 1966-1983 (Box 173)
          - Policy Committee 1967-1974 (Box 173)
          - Upjohn Fellow-Clinical Pharmacy 1968-1971 (Box 173)
      - Interdisciplinary Imaging Research Program 1982 (Box 173)
      - Kaiser-Permanente Award 1976-1982 (Box 173)
      - Kalamazoo Medical Education Program 1971-1973 (Box 173)
      - Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation
        - Correspondence 1971-1980 (Box 173)
        - Project Grants 1969 (Box 173)
        - Summer and Compensatory Programs 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 173)
      - Malpractice Insurance 1970-1979 (Box 173)
      - Measures of Medical Quality
        - General 1976-1977 (Box 173)
        - Information Regarding Uniqueness of the University of Michigan Medical School 1979 (Box 173)
      - Medical Center Audiovisual Committee 1973 (Box 173)
      - Medical Center Journal 1959-1982 (Box 173)
      - Medical Center Review Committee 1973-1974 (Box 173)
      - Medical Library Policies 1975-1982 (Box 173)
      - Medical Science Research Building
        - General 1977-1983, 2 folders (Box 173)
        - Planning Committee 1981-1982 (Box 173)
      - Medical Scientist Training Program 1979-1984 (Box 174)
      - Medical School Class Expansion 1968-1972 (Box 174)
      - Medical School Deanship Review 1977 (Box 178)
      - Medical School Deanship Search 1983-1984 (Box 178)
      - Medical Service Plan Document 1973 (Box 174)
      - Medical Service Plan
        - General 1974-1984 (Box 174)
        - Annual Reports 1982-1983 (Box 174)
        - Audit Reports, 1977-80 (Box 174)
        - Billing System 1980 (Box 174)
        - Building Acquisition 1980 (Box 174)
        - Employee Discount 1977-1980 (Box 174)
        - Long-Term Disability Insurance 1980 (Box 174)
        - Professional Fee Policy Committee 1975 (Box 174)
        - Wayne County 1982-1983 (Box 174)
      - Medical Women's Academic Caucus 1974-1982 (Box 174)
      - Michigan Heart 1969-1973 (Box 174)
      - Michigan Medical Schools Council of Deans
        - Directors 1973-1975 (Box 174)
        - Minutes 1979 (Box 174)
        - Agendas and minutes 1979-1980 (Box 174)
        - Agendas, minutes, correspondence 1981 (Box 174)
        - Agendas, minutes, correspondence 1982-1984 (Box 174)
      - Michigan Historical Collections 1971-1982 (Box 174)
      - Michigan Memorial-Phoenix Project 1959-1969 (Box 174)
      - Microbiological Research Hazards Committee 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 175)
      - Minority Administrator Recruitment 1971-1972 (Box 175)
      - Molecular Genetics
        - General 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box 175)
        - Report to Governor 1982 (Box 175)
      - Mott Foundation 1964-1968 (Box 175)
      - National Fund for Medical Education 1979 (Box 175)
      - National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health 1976-1978 (Box 175)
      - Oakland County-Pontiac Medical Education Program 1974-1981 (Box 175)
      - Oakland University Health Professional Fee Study 1979 (Box 175)
      - Office of Research Administration 1961-1962 (Box 175)
      - Organizational Charts-Medical School 1982-1983 (Box 175)
      - PBB 1977-1978 (Box 175)
      - Primary Care/Community Medicine 1972-1976 (Box 175)
      - Prison Health Care 1978-1980 (Box 175)
      - Prison Health Study 1973-1976 (Box 175)
      - Program Discontinuance
        - Medical Technology 1976-1985 (Box 175)
        - Institute for the Study of Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities (ISMRRD) 1980-1982 (Box 176)
        - Physical Therapy 1980-1982, 3 folders (Box 176)
        - Speech and Hearing Sciences
          - General 1969-1978, 3 folders (Box 176)
          - Camp 1960-1969 (Box 176)
          - Recommendations to Vice President of Academic Affairs on Speech and Hearing Sciences Section 1977 (Box 176)
          - Search Committee 1973-1974 (Box 178)
          - Subcommittee to Review Speech and Hearing Sciences 1973 (Box 176)
      - Rackham Arthritis Research Unit 1963-1967 (Box 176)
      - Research Overhead Costs 1959-1963 (Box 176)
      - School of Nursing 1970-1972 (Box 176)
      - Separate Legal Entity 1984 (Box 176)
      - State Legislature 1975-1983 (Box 176)
      - Statewide House Officers Training System
        - General 1973-1975 (Box 176)
        - General 1976-1982 (Box 177)
      - Strategic Planning 1982 (Box 177)
      - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital
        - Correspondence 1959-1972, 1978-1984, 2 folders (Box 177)
        - Cross-over of Medical Staff Professional Activities 1980-1982 (Box 177)
        - Institutional Liaison Committee 1972 (Box 177)
        - Joint Task Force on Affiliation 1970-1972 (Box 177)
        - Property Acquisition-old St. Joseph Mercy Hospital 1968-1978 (Box 177)
      - Taubman Library
        - Dedication 1980 (Box 177)
        - Funding 1975-1980 (Box 177)
        - Ground Breaking 1977 (Box 177)
        - Site 1975-1980 (Box 177)
      - Tax Equity and Fiscal Responsibility Act (TEFRA)
        - General 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box 177)
        - Reference Papers for the Medicare/Medicaid Regulatory Changes 1983 (Box 177)
      - University Hospital
        - Bed Occupancy 1976-1980 (Box 177)
        - Bylaws 1967-1982 (Box 177)
        - Correspondence 1981-1984 (Box 177)
        - Cost Containment 1979-1981 (Box 177)
        - Hospital Executive Board 1975-1980 (Box 177)
        - Hospital Governance-Hopkins Visit 1980-1983 (Box 177)
        - Nursing Strike 1981 (Box 177)
        - Mott Hospital 1967-1985 (Box 177)
    - 1960-1988
      (Gronvall) (1990 Accession #2)
      - Black Administrator Search 1971 (Box 210)
      - Breazeale, Kelly 1981-1982 (consultant) (Box 179)
      - Cost Allocation Study-Michigan Medical Schools 1972-1981, 2 folders (Box 179)
      - Faverman Report 1980-1982 (Box 179)
      - Medical and Biological Illustration, Reaccreditation (Internal Analysis Report) 1979 (Box 179)
      - Medical School Task Force 1982-1983 (Box 179)
      - Medical Science Building II 1961, 1964 (Box 180)
      - Michigan Medical/Osteopathic School Study Outputs and Costs 1975-1976 (Box 180)
      - Michigan Medical Schools, Council of Deans 1985-1988, 4 folders (Box 180)
      - Physicians Supply 1975-1983 (Box 181)
      - Schools and Colleges (University of Michigan)
        - Dentistry, School of 1966-1984 (Box 181)
        - Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies
          - General 1973-1984 (Box 181)
          - Graduate Program in Physiological Acoustics 1967-1984 (Box 181)
        - Nursing, School of 1980-1983 (Box 181)
        - Public Health, School of 1973-1984 (Box 181)
      - Shapiro, Harold, President 1979-1984 (Box 181)
      - State Health Plan (includes enrollment reports) 1981 (Box 181)
      - Veterans Administration
        - Chief of Staff Search 1984-1987 (Box 210)
        - Correspondence 1984 (Box 181)
        - Dean's Committee 1975-1984 (Box 181)
        - GAO Affiliation Study 1977 (Box 181)
        - Nursing Home Care Dedication 1984 (Box 181)
        - Veterans Readjustment Center 1962-1963 (Box 181)
      - Vice Presidents (University of Michigan)
        - Academic Affairs
          - Harold Shapiro 1977-1979 (Box 181)
          - Billy Frye 1980-1984 (Box 181)
        - Chief Financial Officer (Brinkerhoff) 1978-1984 (Box 181)
        - Development
          - General 1960-1984 (Box 181)
          - Capital Campaign 1977-1985 (Box 182)
          - Committee on Resources 1983 (Box 182)
          - Medical Development Director Search 1984-1985 (Box 182)
        - Research 1970-1980, 2 folders (Box 182)
    - 1960-1990
      - "A" Miscellaneous 1986-1989 (Box 223)
      - Academic Affairs (Dale Report) 1986 (Box 223)
      - Affiliation Agreements 1984-1989 (Box 223)
      - Alumni 1987 (Box 223)
      - Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 223)
      - Affirmative Action 1976-1984 (Box 223)
      - American Medical Association 1989 (Box 223)
      - Archival Review 1984-1987 (Box 223)
      - Association of American Medical Colleges
        - General 1985-1989, 5 folders (Box 223)
        - Institutional Profile Reports 1986-1989 (Box 223)
      - Association for Academic Minority Physicians 1988-1989 (Box 223)
      - Awards 1985-1989, 3 folders (Box 223)
      - "B" Miscellaneous 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 223)
      - Beamount Hospital 1986-1988 (Box 223)
      - Bioengineering 1986-1989 (Box 223)
      - Blodgett Hospital 1988 (Box 224)
      - Blue Cross/Blue Shield 1983-1988, 2 folders (Box 224)
      - Board of Medicine 1986-1987 (Box 224)
      - Bole, Dr. Giles, 1985-1987 (Box 224)
      - Budget 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 224)
      - Burn Center
        - General 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 224)
        - Dr. Irving Feller 1987-1989 (Box 238)
      - "C" Miscellaneous 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 224)
      - Cancer Center 1986-1989, 6 folders
        - Cancer Center Administrator 1987-1988 (Box 225)
        - Letter of Intent 1986 (Box 225)
        - Operating Costs 1988 (Box 225)
      - Center for Public Policy and Research on Organ Transplants 1985-1987 (Box 225)
      - Chelsea Hospital 1985-1987 (Box 225)
      - Chief of Clinical Affairs 1986-1989 (Box 225)
      - Clinical Research Center
        - General 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 225)
        - Site Visit 1989 (Box 225)
      - College of Engineering 1988-1989 (Box 225)
      - College of Pharmacy 1964-1989 (Box 225)
      - Collegiate Institution for Values and Sciences 1985-1987 (Box 225)
      - Cost of Education Study 1983-1985 (Box 225)
      - Council of Deans 1989 (Box 225)
      - "D" Miscellaneous 1984-1989 (Box 225)
      - Dean's Retreat 1987 (Box 225)
      - Department Review Policy and Scheduling 1970-1988 (Box 225)
      - Director of Administration and Financial Affairs 1985-1988 (Box 225)
      - Distinguished University Professorship Nominations 1985-1987 (Box 225)
      - Diagnosis Related Group (DRG) 1984 (Box 225)
      - "E" Miscellaneous 1968-1987 (Box 226)
      - EMG Laboratory 1986-1987 (Box 226)
      - "F" Miscellaneous 1986-1989 (Box 226)
      - Facilities
        - General 1984-1989, 2 folders (Box 226)
        - Medical Administration/ Nursing Building 1988-1989 (Box 226)
      - Faculty
        - Appeal Procedures 1970-1971 (Box 226)
        - Appointment Practices 1984-1989 (Box 226)
        - Clinical 1960-1989, 2 folders (Box 226)
        - Clinical Track 1986-1988, 3 folders (Box 226)
        - Disruption Policy 1969-1970 (Box 226)
        - Fringe Benefits 1969-1988 (Box 226)
        - Governance 1972-1975 (Box 226)
        - Nondiscrimination Policy 1966-1986 (Box 226)
        - Outside Employment 1973-1985 (Box 226)
        - Primary Research 1973-1975 (Box 226)
        - Private Practice Privileges 1960-1975 (Box 226)
        - Promotion Review Procedures 1972-1989 (Box 226)
        - Sabbatical Leave/Off Campus Assignments 1977-1980 (Box 226)
        - Salary 1969, 1986-1988 (Box 226)
        - Tenure 1966-1989 (Box 226)
      - Frederick A. Coller Surgical Society 1972-1989 (Box 226)
      - Freedom of Information Act 1977 (Box 227)
      - Foundations
        - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation 1985-1989 (Box 227)
        - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Minority Grant 1987 (Box 227)
        - Kellogg Foundation 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 227)
        - Pardee Foundation 1988-1989 (Box 227)
        - Lucille P. Markey Trust 1986 (Box 227)
      - "G" Miscellaneous 1985-1989 (Box 227)
      - Green, Dr. Robert 1984-1989 (Box 238)
      - Geriatrics/ Gerontology 1985-1989 (Box 227)
      - Geriatrics Center 1985-1989 (Box 227)